(Penny:)Thanks a lot, guys.
(Bernadette:)What did we do?
(Penny:)Before I made that call,
(Penny:)my pig was alive and happy
(Penny:)and rolling around in the mud.
(Penny:)Now he's illegally buried
in our backyard
(Penny:)next to my great-grandmother.
(Amy:)Really?
(Bernadette:)They didn't eat him?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Penny:)He was a beloved member
of the family.
(Bernadette:)The breakfast meat family?
(Penny:)It's not funny.
(Penny:)You're up.
Call your mother.
(Amy:)Oh, maybe later.
(Amy:)Your pig dying
made me sad.
(Amy:)And a little hungry.
(Penny:)Phone, now.
(Amy:)Okay. Okay.
(Amy:)Fine.
(Amy:)Hi, Mom.
(Penny:)Try dialing.
(Amy:)You saw that, huh?
(Amy:)Hi, Mom. How are you doing?
(Amy:)Oh, good.
(Amy:)How's work?